xtra-pc.com 2019-04-04

# Privacy Policy — Xtra-PC

Last Updated on May 15,2018. This privacy policy is effective immediately.

## Introduction

At Xtra-PC (the “Company” or “We”), we respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it  
through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when  
you visit this website (our “Website”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting  
and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On this Website.
  * In e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website.
  * Through mobile and desktop applications you download from this Website, which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and this Website.
  * When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or
  * any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information  
and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use  
our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may  
change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be  
acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

## Children Under the Age of 13

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any  
personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from  
children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or  
through any of its features/register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website, use any of  
the interactive or public comment features of this Website or provide any information about yourself to  
us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name  
you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13  
without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have  
any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us via our contact us link.

## Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address,  
telephone number or ANY OTHER INFORMATION THE WEBSITE COLLECTS THAT IS  
DEFINED AS PERSONAL OR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION UNDER  
AN APPLICABLE LAW (“personal information”);
  * that is about you but individually does not identify you, and/or
  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may  
include usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies, web beacons and  
other tracking technologies.
  * From third parties, for example, our business partners.

## Information You Provide to Us.

The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information  
provided at the time of registering to use our Website, subscribing to our service, posting  
material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a  
problem with our Website.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us.
  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders.  
You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our  
Website.
  * Your search queries on the Website.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “posted”) on public areas  
of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, “User  
Contributions”). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk.  
Although we limit access to certain pages/you may set certain privacy settings for such information by  
logging into your account profile, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or  
impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you  
may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we

## Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies.

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection  
technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns,  
including:

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, and other  
communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating  
system and browser type.

We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and  
across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking). The information we collect  
automatically is statistical data and does not include personal information, but we may maintain it or  
associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us  
to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us  
to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your  
computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on  
your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of  
our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our  
system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
  * Flash Cookies. Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies)  
to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our  
Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser  
cookies.
  * Web Beacons. Pages of our the Website may contain small electronic files known as web  
beacons (also referred to as clear gifs. pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company,  
for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an e-mail and for other  
related website statistics (for example, recording

We do not collect personal Information automatically, but we may tie this information to personal information about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us.

## Third-party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies.

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third-parties,  
including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers and application providers. These third  
parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to  
collect information about you when you use our website. The information they collect may be  
associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal  
information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online  
services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or  
other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any  
questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider  
directly.

## How We Use Your Information

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal  
information:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
  * To provide you with information about our services
  * To provide you with notices about your account/subscription, including expiration and renewal  
notices.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into  
between you and us, including for billing and collection.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide  
though it.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * To fulfill any purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our  
advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these  
purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the  
advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

## Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any  
individual, without restriction.  
We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy  
policy:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who  
are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only  
for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization,  
dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Company’s assets, whether as a going  
concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal  
information held by the Company about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have consented to these  
disclosures. We contractually require these third parties to keep personal information  
confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. For example, if you give us an e-mail address to  
use the “e-mail a friend” feature of our Website, we will transmit the contents of that e-mail and  
your e-mail address to the recipients.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government  
or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements, including for billing and collection  
purposes.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of  
the Company, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other  
companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have  
created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * Tracking Technologies and Advertising. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser  
cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash  
cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s website. If you disable or refuse  
cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function  
properly.
  * We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based  
advertising. However these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your  
information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from  
members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) on the NAI’s website.

## Accessing and Correcting Your Information

You may send us an e-mail via our contact link to request access to, correct or delete any personal  
information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also  
deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the  
change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain  
viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users.  
Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including User Contributions, is  
governed by our terms of use.

## Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to  
request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their  
direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us via the contact us link.

## Data Security

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and  
from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where  
you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping  
this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we  
do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal  
information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk.  
We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the  
Website.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material  
changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you by e-mail to the e-mail  
address specified in your account and/or through a notice on the Website home page. The date the  
privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we  
have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our  
Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

## Contact Information

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Site, or wish to  
withdraw your consent for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your Personal Information,  
please contact us by sending an email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Thank You for Visiting the Website.
